[suspenseful music playing]
[man whimpering and panting]
No! [grunts]
-[squealing]
-No! Get off! Get away!
[squealing intensifies]
Spiders all over me!
[screaming]
[hisses]
[dramatic music playing]
[crowd murmuring]
[suspenseful music playing]
[theme music playing]
Tired of searching for subtitles?
Ray generates them instantly: getray.app
[dramatic music playing]
[Barbara] Thanks for coming
on such short notice. Renee.
Honestly. compared to my day today.
this is a treat.
If you saw half the stuff
I'm juggling right now...
I know my dad stuck you with Flass.
That can't be any kind of fun.
Yeah. watching that guy
is definitely a full-time job.
[inhales] So... your case?
My client has psychological issues.
and I need a doctor to examine him.
then testify.
But I'm having no luck
finding one who's good
and has trial experience.
[sighs]
I really miss Harleen.
Oh... sorry about that.
I know you two were getting close.
Yeah...
I was gonna take her ice skating
after the first snow.
Now Winter's half over. and...
I know.
If they'd found her body. at least
we could grieve and move on.
But it's like she's still out there.
Um. listen.
I'll definitely ask around for the name
of a good shrink for your case.
[bell dings]
You keeping an eye on him.
or is he keeping an eye on you?
What are ya doin' here. Flass?
We're partners. ain't we?
Ms. Gordon.
Sorry to break up whatever this is here.
but me and her need to move.
We got another college crazy.
-Ah. jeez. That's five now.
-Yeah. so chop. chop!
College crazies?
Kids flipping out. winding up dead.
Are they murders? Overdoses? Who knows.
Montoya. let's go!
Yeah. yeah. keep your pants on!
-Thanks for the coffee.
-Absolutely.
[dramatic music playing]
[camera snaps]
I'm sorry about this. Mr. Wayne.
Your foundation doesn't hand out
endowments like candy.
We like to commemorate the occasion.
Gotham U was my father's alma mater
and mine.
I'm embarrassed it took something like
this to remind me of my responsibilities.
Ah. yes. These student deaths.
They have cast a bit of a pall
on the Greek Week festivities.
but the board is confident
that this will blow over soon.
Are those police detectives?
[provost]
Indeed! The GCPD is being very helpful.
Keeping the whole thing
out of the press for now. [chuckles]
Sorry to break in. we still need
some solo shots of Mr. Wayne.
and the light's much better
over by the science building.
I'm in your hands. Ms. Vale.
Do with me as you will.
Thomas Dalton was a student of yours.
He never talked to you
about his mental state?
I teach chemistry. not psychology.
I have hundreds of students.
And I don't have time to involve myself
in their personal lives.
"Esoteric chemicals
and their interactions?"
Yes. but I'm afraid the details of my work
would be far too technical
for you to under...
Yup. Got it. Thanks. professor.
If you think of anything that could
help us. don't hesitate to call.
Okay. you say the victim was running.
but no one was chasing him.
Nobody said nothin'. man.
No spiders. nobody chasin' the guy.
Nothin'.
Uh. Carmine. right?
Did you know the victim?
[scoffs] Me? No way.
Just another poindexter on campus.
At least one of those shrimps
goes screwy every semester.
Hey. Tami! Let me carry those books.
What about you kid? Anything to add?
Not really. sir.
Thomas was a good student is all.
Can't believe this happened to him.
[chuckles] Yeah. thrilling.
You can go now.
You think of something to add. call.
We about done here. Montoya?
Why? You got someplace else to be?
Talkin' to these kids
is like watchin' grass grow.
[Renee] We've got five victims
in five weeks.
all hallucinating before they died.
We need to light a fire under the medical
examiner to get that tox report done.
Say. could I get copies of those?
You can have anything you want.
I... I mean. sure. Yeah. no problem.
I'll have them sent to your estate.
[jazz music playing]
[Harleen] Overeating won't solve
your marital issues. Herman.
Wilma knows you're cheating on her.
and she knows you know she knows.
Someone's canophilia
is getting out of hand.
That is truly an advanced case of
ideational apraxia you have there. Max.
But you do hide it well.
[sighs] If there's one thing
I'm an expert at...
it's hiding.
[jazz music continues]
[keys jangling]
-[door unlocks]
-[gasps] Hmm?
Honey. I'm home.
[Harleen] Renee! [sighs in relief]
-How was your day?
-Long.
I'm beat.
A university student was screaming
about spiders attacking him
before he dropped dead.
Probably a heart attack.
Definitely not spiders.
Could be the result of a brain tumor.
Maybe a psychotic break.
Do you have the blood toxicology?
-It could be that...
-[Renee] Uh-uh.
No way. You are not pushing
that cute little nose in an active case.
-Sorry. babe.
-[sighs]
I'm just trying to help.
I barely see you lately.
I'm holed up in here.
Everyday. Alone.
And I'm harboring a fugitive.
Anybody sees me out on the town
with Dr. Harleen Quinzel...
Who is presumed dead.
Whose picture was front page
on every paper for a month.
And is presumed dead.
Harleen.
Look.
-Gimme a minute to change and...
-You'll make it up to me?
Trust me. I'm a cop.
[dramatic music playing]
Did you find anything unusual
in the campus photographs?
Only the lovely camera woman's
phone number.
written on the back of every photo.
The young ladies nowadays.
fresh as paint.
-[Alfred] Where to now. sir?
-The morgue.
Ah. tissue samples. I presume.
I need to see if there are any exotic
chemicals in the victim's blood.
These could be murders. Pennyworth.
[engine revs]
[dramatic music playing]
Five of them?
Identical symptoms...
That's not a coincidence.
That's a field test.
Hey. Renee. did you notice this...
[dramatic music continues]
Dead boy number three.
Now. the co-eds.
Two dead girls.
Three dead boys.
Huh.
[distorted voice] Hands off.
That's my body.
Sorry.
Did I scare you?
It would take a lot more than you've got.
Let's test that theory.
[suspenseful music playing]
[glass shattering]
You...
[grunts]
[fighting grunts and pants]
[yawns] I am so sorry.
I passed right out.
-[door buzzer]
-Harleen. Why are you ringin' the...
Good. You're already dressed.
Or is that still...
[chuckles] No nightcap for baby Gordon.
-Well. guess I pegged that wrong.
-What do you want. Flass?
Break in. City morgue.
Somebody tossed the joint.
Dalton. Our evidence!
There she is. Back in the game.
[dramatic music playing]
[gasps]
-You're making a mistake. I'm innocent.
-The innocent don't run.
And sane people don't dress like bats
and do detective work for free.
Who's your partner?
He's not my... [sighs]
He didn't want me touching the bodies.
[inhales] I guess he's the one
who scared those kids to death.
Delusions don't kill people.
If they're chemically induced
and amplified. they can.
I'm a medical doctor. remember?
Psychiatrist.
I know what I'm talking about.
[metal clangs]
If you turn me in. you lose my expertise.
-I wanna solve this case as much as you.
-Why?
All right. Indulge your obsession.
Interrogate me.
Meanwhile. an obvious psychopath
is going after his next victim.
There will be more.
That's better.
It shows your mania
doesn't dominate your common...
-[spray hisses]
-[sighs]
-[ears ringing]
-[Harleen groans]
[sighing]
[gasps]
[groaning. panting]
[sighs]
I forgot. Murder isn't part of
your pathology.
So... this is where you live.
This has to be the result
of some significant childhood trauma.
-The last time we talked we...
-You tried to kill me.
Fair. I did.
But not very hard.
You said Dalton was scared to death.
How?
The police report said he died screaming
about bugs that weren't there.
Yes. I saw the police reports.
No. I'm not saying how.
GCPD only has two detectives
working this case.
You're not in Flass' circle.
Why is Montoya shielding you?
She's not! She is...
You know what.
that's none of your business.
Your mania is catching criminals.
Let's stick to that.
[Batman] David Mortimer.
Would've graduated this year
with a degree in applied chemistry.
Rebecca Cloonan. PhD candidate. chemistry.
Bill Sprang. freshman. molecular biology.
Plus Mary Fradon and Thomas Dalton.
That's five.
Age range. 19-25.
All afraid of invisible threats.
[Batman] Spiders. rats. clowns...
One ran off a bridge.
One slit his own throat in order
to purge the demons.
Definitely a field test.
-A field test...
-It's pretty obvious.
Controlled environment. the campus.
Limited pool. the students.
Age range.
Someone's testing a drug.
The victims all have this man in common.
Professor Charles Burton.
[party murmurings]
I... [sharp inhale] don't think
that's appropriate. professor.
I'm a student.
[nervous chuckle] I'm your student.
[sighs] There's nothing
to be afraid of. Jane.
You're a grown woman.
It's perfectly acceptable
to make your own adult choices.
I'm... uncomfortable even talking
about this. sir.
Perhaps if we move
somewhere more private...
Okay. professor. That's enough.
She said no. sir.
[chuckles] You young men
are making a serious error here.
-I was just simply...
-Takin' a walk. Right?
Your point is made. Mr. Broome.
Junior. I'll deal with you later.
young man.
He's gone. Jane. It's all over.
Can I get ya some apple cider?
It'll pick ya right up!
Thanks. Junior.
I think I'm just gonna go back
to the sorority house and go to bed.
Apple cider? That was your move?
Brother. you are a poindexter.
Come on. little man. Let me tell you
all about the birds and the bees.
-[dramatic music playing]
-[crickets chirping]
[distorted breathing]
-[whoosh]
-[leaves rustling]
Professor Burton?
If that's you. I'm gonna call the police.
right now!
[panting] Yes. sir. Gotham U. Yes. sir.
Detective Flass said I should call
if I... I thought of something on the case.
And I think someone's been
following me. And...
Yes. Yes. sir. He has my address.
Yes. I'll stay here.
[deep sigh]
[suspenseful music playing]
-[suspenseful music continues]
-[engine revs]
[groans]
You could've just blindfolded me.
So it's Jane Overstreet?
-The sorority girl?
-She fits the pattern.
She's in one of Burton's classes.
We still don't know
how he's delivering the drug.
[Jane screaming]
The house is on fire! Flames all around!
[gasping] Help! Help me!
[distorted voice]
But I am helping you. Jane.
More importantly. you're helping me.
-[Jane screams]
-[intense music playing]
[grunts]
-Hallucinogen. Has to be alkaloid-based.
-The flames! Closer! We're surrounded!
-What cuts alkaloid?
-I'm trapped!
[gasping and groaning]
[Harleen] Milk.
[grunts]
[distorted voice]
No! I'm not finished!
-[smoke hissing]
-[gasps]
-[distorted groan]
-[suspenseful music continues]
[screaming]
Quinzel!
Harleen!
[gasping]
[ominous music playing]
[panting]
[groans]
[gasps]
Renee? Help me! Get me out!
I need to get out!
Renee!
[ominous music continues]
[groaning]
[Batman. echoing] Quinzel! Fight it!
It's not real!
Whatever you're seeing isn't real!
[struggling]
[straining] Milk...
-[Jane gasping]
-Neutralizes alkaline.
[Jane panting]
No. the fire is all over me!
I'm burning up. I gotta put it out!
-The lake! I gotta jump in the lake!
-Jane!
-No!
-[screaming]
[body thuds]
[dramatic music playing]
[sighs]
-[car engine running]
-[breaks slam]
[doors close]
[Flass] Looks like we got number six.
[grappling gun fires]
[ominous music playing]
[crowd cheering]
[panting] She saw me.
She looked right at me.
The gas weapon is obviously
the delivery system.
The costume is a disguise.
but it also protects him from the gas.
I went through her files.
I'm outside. and I'm...
This again!
I told myself I was helping.
But I've compromised her.
Quinzel. focus.
Right.
You're right.
Burton's obviously psychotic.
with delusional ideations
and obsessive patterns.
Well. we just broke that pattern.
So what's his next move. doctor?
[dramatic music playing]
-Professor Burton.
-Hello. Junior.
It's time we talked about you
interfering in my life.
[ominous music playing]
These are presentation papers
for something he calls.
an "alkaline-based phobic
instigator agent."
Photos of the dead students.
His students.
He had a partner for some of this.
Jonathan Crane. Jr.
My psych teacher
was named Jonathan Crane.
His son. maybe?
Crane was Burton's teaching assistant.
Come on!
[door creaks open]
[suspenseful music playing]
Right diagnosis. Wrong subject.
Crane's the killer.
He helped Burton
make the fear chemical.
Burton aborts the project as unethical.
Crane feels abandoned.
The project is his whole identity.
You broke his pattern. he's adrift.
He's got three options.
Vanish. go out in a blaze of glory.
or both.
You'd make a fair psychiatrist.
if you weren't so damaged.
Go.
I'm no hero.
I didn't get into this to save the day.
Hm.
Classic monomania.
-[smoke hissing]
-[groaning]
[distorted voice] Idiots! Fools!
All of you. nothing but clusters of fear!
Fear of ridicule!
That's gelotophobia.
Fear of not fitting in. autophobia.
-Fear of...
-Hey!
What the hell. guy?
What do you think you're do...
[coughing]
[screaming]
[whimpering]
-Fear of never shutting the hell up!
-[whimpering]
Oh. my God. It's coming!
It's coming!
Don't you see?
Jonathan Crane.
-[grunts]
-[smoke hisses]
[coughing]
[dramatic music playing]
[Jonathan] I wish I could see it.
Your fear.
Is it agoraphobia?
Fear of open spaces?
-[people screaming in the distance]
-Maybe heliophobia. fear of sunlight.
[screaming continues]
[grunts. groans]
Or maybe you're overcompensating.
-Is it something more obvious?
-[Old Batman] No...
[Jonathan]
Is it... Could it be chiroptophobia?
[Old Batman] No.
Fear...
[Jonathan] That's the fear of bats.
No...
fear.
[Jonathan] Did a bat scare you as a child?
[Batman] No...
fear!
No... fear!
What? No! How?
-[groans]
-[smoke hisses]
Fear is a poison.
-[coughs]
-Fear is a weapon.
But fear is never in control!
-[dramatic music playing]
-[monstrous roaring]
[Jonathan] No. stop!
You can't! You can't do this!
-[monstrous growl]
-[groans]
-[monstrous grunt]
[groans. gasps]
[growling]
-[dramatic music continues]
-[whimpering in fear]
[distorted] Look at me. Crane.
-What do you see?
-[Jonathan whimpering]
[screaming]
[body thuds]
[dramatic music playing]
[soft music playing]
You came.
My girl left me a note.
You gonna tell me what tonight was about?
We both knew we were on a clock.
One of us just had to admit it.
It's not too late.
-We can...
-Shush.
No. We can't.
Keeping my secret is drowning you.
I really can't have that.
You gave me a gift.
You let me dream for a while.
Time to wake up.
[distant police sirens]
My ride's here.
Don't wait up.
[sirens continue]
[dramatic music continues]
[car brakes slam]
[credits music playing]
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm